Guide to the Josiah K. Lilly Correspondence, 1931-1944 CAM.JKLCorr.2016
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- TA TE, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 589)
  Correspondence with Rev. Francis H. Tetu; C.G. Talbott; Tennessee Dept. of Education; Temple University; University of Texas; Tacoma Public Library; N.F. Tarrant; Maggie Taylor; W.T. Cash; Leon Taylor; John Tarleton Agricultural College; Samuel Tanenbaum; Taylor University; Marilyn Ruth Teegardin; Ella Tate; Woodrow Wilson Junior High Terre Haute, IN; Sylvia Tannenbaum; Terre Haute Public Library; L.H. Thackaberry; Tabernacle Presbyterian Church; Thurston Thacher; Roosevelt School Tacoma WA; KMO Tacoma; WEDAE Tampa; Francis Taylor; Winona Tank; John F. Tait; Albert Taylor; George W. Turner; Mary Thermos; Loretta Tarpy; G.W. Ternes; Mildred Teboe; N.B. Tarkington; Florence Marie Taylor; Albert A. Taylor; Laurel Connell Thayer
- THO THY TI TO, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 590)
  Correspondence with E.S.L. Thompson; S. Tittler; University of Toronto; Laura Thompson; W.J. Thompson; Ernest Thorla; Elizabeth Tolle; Martin Thomson Jr.; University of Toledo; Tipton Public Library; Toronto Concert Band; Oakdale School Toledo; Timms & Howard Inc.; Lewis M. Thompson; Martha Townsend; Blanche Thompson; Buddy Thompson; Leah Thomas; R. Bruce Tom; Warren Foundation Library, Three Oaks MI; Gertrude L. Thompson; F.M. Thomas; Tourist Club of Noblesville; Frederic M.L. Townsend; Paul Townsend; Tomah Public Library; Topeka Music Studio; Tipton Public Library; Wm F. Thornton
- Townsend, John Wilson, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 591)
  Correspondence with John Wilson Townsend of Lexington, KY. Townsend was an exuberant, enthusiastic, unscrupulous, and tenacious, with a great many contacts with the old established families in Lexington. Townsend grew to feel that he had a personal stake in both Lilly and the Collection after it had become established (especially in the case of J.T. Howard). In addition, Townsend was a rumor-monger, often inaccurate. Very little of value came to Lilly through this man, but he was the one to supply a first edition of "The Social Orchestra."
- TR TU TW TY, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 592)
  Correspondence with Tuesday Musical Club; Trinity Court Studio; Anna Bailey Trowbridge; Typographic Service Co.; Tulane University; Samuel L. Trotcky; Charles E. Tuttle; Concord Township School; Phyllis Trogus; Fred L. Trask; Janey M. Trace; Harry C. Turner; A.J. Treat & Son, Inc.; KVOA Tuscon; KTUL Tulsa; Charlotte Trout; Alden L. Tyler; M.L. Turtelot; Alden Tyler; Traverse City Public Library; Alta Gene Trimer; Transylvania College
- U, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 593)
  Correspondence with U.S. Army; United States Marine Band; US Federal Music Project; US Library of Congress; August Urdl; US Marine Corps; Union Theological Seminary; Floyd Unger; US Army 7th Infantry; US Army 35th Infantry; R.A. Urquhart; Union City Free Public Library; Utica Public Library; University of Utah; USS Arkansas; University Book and Antique Shop; George Urmy; US Navy; US Special Service Squadron; A.N. Uhler; Carlos V. Urrutia; US Dept of Interior; Ursuline Academy; William Treat Upton; University Book Service
- US Library of Congress, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 594)
  Correspondence with the U.S. Library of Congress. Acknowledgements of materials Lilly donated.
- V, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 595)
  Correspondence with Christos Vrionides; James Van Dyck; Victor Distributing Corp; Village Green Antique Shop; Volga Public Schools; Virginia State Teacher's College; Vanderbilt University; Vinton Library Club; Virginia Federation of music clubs; Valparaiso University; Virginia State Library; University of Vermont; Vermont State Library; Vineland Historical and Antiquarian Society; Bob Voges; C.C. Vatter; J.B. Vandaworker; Daisy L. Van Gordon; Village Book Shop; Van Der Veer Company; Alan Valentine; Village Green Antique Shop; Van Norman Book Company; John Van Deventer; Charles Voyles; Valley Stream Central High School; Milton Vaughan; R.S. Van Loon; Raymond Valentine; W.D. Vinson; Valley Mills Home Economic Club; Vroman's Book Store; Glen E. Veach; Vincennes Public Library
- Van Leeuwen, Ary, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 596)
  Correspondence with Ary Van Leeuwen. Another entrepreneur looking for financial backing, Van Leeuwen never specifies what kind of support he is looking for.
- Vidas, Raoul Georges, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 597)
  Correspondence with Raoul Georges Vidas of New York, NY. A violinist and a Foster fan, Vidas was introduced to Lilly by Lorraine Foster. Vidas was invited to play at the dedication of the Pittsburgh Memorial and made arrangements of several Foster songs for violin, piano, and full symphony.
- Village Studio, The, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 598)
  Correspondence with The Village Studio in New York City, owned by Earle Goodman, a small time dealer.
- Virginia University, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 599)
  Correspondence with Virginia University. Acknowledgements of materials Lilly donated.
- WAA WAP, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 600)
  Correspondence with R.E. Wallace; Small; Alice J. Caron; Howard A. Nettleton; Dorothy J. Black; Cobby de Stivers; Axtell; Dorothy J. Black; J.W. Wainwright; Harriet E. Wall; Charles Wagner; Raymond Walters; Small; Frank M. Wallace; Donald F. Mallin; Merle Walker; E.T. Waldo; Vogt; Maple; Mary T. Waite; H.E. Studebaker; Philip B. Wallace; Joseph Sexton; Allan B. Sly; Aleda Waggoner; Alice C. Persons; Lela Walls; Alada Wagoner; Thomas E. Christmen; Merl Wagner; Ruth S. Reynolds
- WAR-WAZ WEA-WEH, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 601)
  Correspondence with C.R.. Armstrong; Richard Warner; Ward-Brodt Music Co.; E.B. Ward; E.B. Nard; George F. Bowerman; Small; Lilla Atherton; Ward Edwards; John R. Mason; Mary B. Taylor; Karl George; Charles W. Smith; Beulah Wayland; George Simpson; Jacqueline Wedekind; Myrtle Weatherholt; Harry Weier; I. Warshaw; E.M. Webster; A.A. White; Paul E. Harding; Pearl Warner; Howard V. Weens; Frank Weer; I. Warshaw; Lloyd E. Squier; Carleton D. Smith; LeRoy Mark; L.F. Weatherwax; Mary Watson; Oscar Wegelin; Edwin H. Hughes; Janet Clark; Oliver Strunk; John Russell Mason; H. J. Jett; Simms; E.Z. Posell; W.W. Foote; Ruth A. Kerr
- WEI-WER WES-WEZ, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 602)
  Correspondence with Geneve Weibel; Charles Edward Mayhew; Robert D. Steele; Dorothy J. Black; Weidlein; Edward Welch; Robert Grant; Small; Mary T. Leiper; Myron Vandenburgh; E. Piehl; M. M. Ward; E.D. Roberts; Grace W. Cotts; M.E. Barrett; Betty Jean Wents; J. Weil; Goldie Welty; Franklin F. Holbrook; A. Enna; A. Enna; Janet Weke; Monroe Whitmoyer; A.D. Rose; Mary Lou Weidner; Mrs. Cliff Westerfield; Marion Foster Welch; Leah Curnutt; Pirtle; Leland D. Baldwin; Maple; Harry E. Weier; L.D. Arnett; W.H. Patlieart; Fred Landon
- Werner & Co., Edgar S., 1935 (Box 18, Folder 603)
  Correspondence with Edgar S. Werner & Co. In 1935, this company, at Lilly's request sent Foster Hall a pantomime, with drawings of "Old Folks at Home." This was printed in Foster Hall Bulletin 11. Werner's complained of copyright infringement, but Whittlesey ascertained that the copyright had expired in 1928. No further complaints are made.
- WH, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 604)
  Correspondence with Joseph White; E.T. Whiter; Charles W. Whittlesey; Dorothy R. White; Dorothy J. Black; Cullen White; Julia E. Blanchard; Marcus Skarstiell; D. Sterling Wheelwright; Small; Madge Whiteman; Esther Whitman; Alice G. Whitmire; Mary D. Murphy; J.H. Whittey; Ruth Eileen White; J.H. Whitty; Olive Wharton; Robert J. White; Mrs. Amelia White; Maple; Florence White
- Whittlesey, Walter R., 1935 (Box 19, Folder 605)
  Correspondence with Walter R. Whittlesey of Washington DC. Whittlesey was an employee of the Library of Congress. His initial contacts with Lilly consisted of answering various questions from the Foster Hall staff. In 1932 he was forced to retire from the Library, but because by that time he was engaged in research for Lilly he was allowed to maintain a desk there and continue his work. After his retirement, Lilly began paying him a monthly allowance. Whittlesey's work was to aid in the systematic coordination of Lilly's collection, verification of facts (copyright, etc.), checking over the reproductions for flaws, assisting E.F. Morneweck in the writing of the Chronicles, mounting such ephemeral material as newspaper clippings, and so on. In short, his high degree of professionalism made him invaluable to the development of the collection. When he died in 1936, his daughter (Katherine Copley), who was already assisting him, remained in Lilly's employment and continued her father's work.
- Whitlock's Book Store, Inc., 1935 (Box 19, Folder 606)
  Correspondence with Whitlock's Book Store, Inc., an original book dealer associated with Foster Hall
- WIA-WIE WIG-WIL, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 607)
  Correspondence with Ezra Williams; Willis Music Company; Laurence B. Ellert; Viola Wilke; Frances Wilkins; F.S. Evans; Warner Williams; Frederic Allen Williams; George E. Williams; Mrs. George E. Williams; D.E. Wilcox; Small; Wilmington Public Library; Mary A. Williamson; Dorothy J. Black; Howard Thomson; Raymond Walters; Catherine T. Shulenberger; E.G. Swem; A.L. Bailey; Mary Baker; Harold H. Wich; Edgar Willis; Albert E. Wier; Chloe Willis; T.A. Haga; Dorothy Willard; T.A. Haga; Barbara Wilcox; Wieland; Albert E. Wier; Albert Wilkes; Ethel H. Kuening; Mrs. George Williams; Charles F. Fischer; Theodore H. Willis; George Williams; Charles L. Wilhelm; E. G. Williams; Russel L. Lowe; John H. Stenger; Carl J. Wicklund; George E. Wiliams; Lawrence B. Ellert; Ezra Williams; Lucy Eugene Osborne; Mapple; Chapin Library; Helen Will; Mary Neikick Baker; Mayme Kennison
- Wilson, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 608)
  Correspondence with Wilson Law Office; Mrs. W. Wayne Wilson; Stallings; Small; H.W. Wilson; Black; Axtell; Evelyn F. Morneweck; Samuel M. Wilson; Peggy Wilson; Emett Wilson; Julia Wilson; Ruth Wilson; Samuel M. Wilson
- Wilson, Mary A., 1935 (Box 19, Folder 609)
  Correspondence with Mary A. Wilson [see also Johnson, Mary E.] of Indianapolis, IN. One of two disabled typists employed by the Hall. After the Collection was moved to Pittsburgh she continued to work for Mr. Hodges long distance. Among other tasks she helped to type Mrs. Morneweck's manuscript of The Chronicles.
- WIN-WIS WIT-WIZ, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 610)
  Correspondence with Mary E. Titus; Walter Grimm; Elmer B. Funk; Joseph Schafer; Windsor Library Association; William F. Yust; Vernon Eddy; W.M. Smith; Small; Theodore Winkle; Tillie Windler; Beth T. Clurk; Axtell; G.F. Patton; Richard Kounts; Grace E. Winters; Jeanie M. Turner; William F. Lust; Ida J. Dacus; john M. Wise; Matthew Winters; Frederick Fuller
- Witmark & Sons, M., 1935 (Box 19, Folder 611)
  Correspondence with Richard Kountz, Lyle Dowling, Dorothy Black, Copy of Agreement between Lilly and M. Witmark and Sons, puiblisher of "Songs of Stephen Foster" dated April 10, 1935. Mr. Maple, Mr, Dowling, Mr. Axtell
- Wohlgemuth, E. Jay, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 612)
  Correspondence with E. Jay Wohlgemuth of Cincinnati. This man was instrumental in the formation of the Cincinnati University Memorial Room. Lilly donated a great deal of material to this collection. The file includes the dedication of the Ivone statue and various other materials to Foster. It also contains research into Foster's life in Cincinnati.
- WO-WR WU-WY, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 613)
  Correspondence with Small; Lindsay Workman; Axtell; P.H. Wohlford; Agnes Wolcott; Hazel Delphine; Harry Wurtzel; Robert Shaw; Irving McDonald; Edith Baker; Wallace B. Worwood; Marjorie Wolfer; Dorothy Black; Eloise Wolfer; Henrietta Little; Wallace Wolfolk; W.A. Wooldridge; Grace E. Wyclkoff; Wolfer Printing Co.; Woods Brothers; Elizabeth F. Wolfe; Mary R. Tolbert; Richard S. Wormser; Theodore Wukesch; Louise Wolf; Herman A. Wohl; Jule Safford Woodruff; Maple; Alexander Woollcott; Anna Lee Wolfe; Samuel Wheeler Worthington; Thomas N. Wynne; Anna M. Deyo; Elizabeth Talley
- Wood, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 614)
  Correspondence with Dorothy Black; Wood; Mrs. Wood
- Woodward, Florence, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 615)
  Correspondence with Florence Woodward, a small scale dealer in Missouri.
- Wright, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 616)
  Correspondence with Edith Wright. Many first editions and early sheet music came from this individual.
- X-Y-Z, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 618)
  Correspondence with Mildred Young; Dorothea Yaeger; Joseph Zarcone; Jay Yohe; Ada Showers; Grace Young; Leon Miller; Dorothy Schwartzer; M. Zorn. Harry Peterson; Economy Drug Store; Lou Finkbinder; Reginald Fink; Dorothy Black; Sarah Stranathan; Leora Ludwig; Dorothea Yeager; Eva J. O'Meara; Eva J. OMeara; John N. Yalton; Kathryn Watson; Mary Zidek; Sixth grade Pupils; Lillian Brennel; Grace Kerner; L.N. Dailey; Kathryn Roemer; Blanche McCracken; Elenora Brooks; Grace M. Fanton; Elena Ortiz de Zevallos; A.L. Holfram; Edward Yarborough; Valley Broadcasters; R.L. Harlow; Arthur Zinkin; Charles Rush; Evelyn Young; Mrs. Charles Yorbrough; Theodore Marsdall; A. E. Martin; Elena Ortiz de Zevallos; Stark Young; Helen Winston
- Otto Zimmerman and Sons Co., 1935 (Box 19, Folder 619)
  Correspondence with Otto Zimmerman and Sons, Co. Lilly conducted business with this company on a sporadic basis. This company printed the Guzman Band Medley.
- Acknowledgements of Foster Hall Publications, 1932 (Box 19, Folder 620)
  Correspondence with J.I. Curtis; E. Smith; Isabel Turner; Dora Caldwell; M. Wade; Ruth Blair; John Atherton; Emma Hatele; C.K. Bolton; State Library of Massachusetts; Milton Lord; Harvey Brooks; Mildred Buchanan; Bucknell Library; A.H. Shearer; Walter L. Brown; G. D. Smith; E. Beach; Effie Lansden; Wm. homer Ames; The Newberry Library; Charles Hadley; Earl Manchester; M.T. Brown; Lilian Cuthbert; Henry Marx; Ethel F. McCollough; G.E. Marsh; Ida B. Mutch; Marjourie Wethrebee; A. Fiske; Joseph Harrison; Frank C. Patten; Gertrude MacKenney; Charles S. Thayer; Edward L. Gookin; Mabel Miller; Marie Hamlin; John Holland; James Prendergast Free Library; L. Helen Berkey; Lena B. Nofcier; Kleine; Helen B. Umble; Lulu Horne
- Whittlesey, Walter R., 1936 (Box 19, Folder 621)
- Acknowledgements of "My Brother Stephen", 1932 (Box 19, Folder 622)
  Correspondence with Milton T. Ford; Charles N. Boyd; Frank Grant Lewis; D.L. Chambers; Public Library of Cincinnati; Harry J. Holcombe; Mabel L. Krueger; Joseph Harrison; Joseph M. Francis; Edith L. Genn; Frank C. Groover; Augustus H. Shearer; E.Y. Guernsey; William S. Hall; Credo Harris; Harry Harris; Marie Hamlin; Belle Hershman; George C. Hitt; J.D. Hoffman; Julius W. Hulff; Florence Venn; Esther Nitt;M. Jillian; C.B. Jordan; W.F. Kelleher; Lena B. Nofcier; Joseph Klein; J. Leon Lascoff; C. P. Lesh; Sara Linton; Harold Brigham; Martindale; Frank J. Metcalf; Noah Morrison; H.P. Morton; G. Barret Moxley; Eda Pape; Ralph Munn; Florence Williams; John Haward Dice; Barbara [ ]; Mabel Ahern; E. Smith; J.W. Sturmer; Mary Ward; Liter; J.H. Whitty; Good; Edith Wycoff
- Significance Replies, 1932 (Box 19, Folder 623)
  Correspondence with Susan Himmelwright; Margaret Wade; Brown; Frank Lewis; C.S. Wright; Ethel McCollough; M.M. Colerick; Friends Free Library; Jean Smith; John Russell Hayes; M.E. Stuvo; W.F. Richardson; Vernie Baldwin; Bertha E. Schomo; Harrodsburgh Publich Library; Susan Startling Towles; Johnson Brigham; Lena B. Nofcier; A.l. Brackbill; Charles Norton; E.H. Redstone; T. Wilson Hedley; Mary Snyder; E. Moch; A.L. Clark; James Wyer; Paul R. Byrne; Jessie M. Mauck; M.R. Kneule; H.E. Hofmann; Agnes D. MacDonald; J. Howard Dice; Harold A. Wooster; W.M. Hepburn; T.A. Johnson; Charles Shaw; Katherin E. Bowder; J. Kitchell; H.R. McIlwaine; H.S. Wedding; Janet M. Clark; Clifford R. Myers; H.H. Cherry; Mary Leiper; H. Long; Mary Baker
- Record of Foster Hall Mailings: Bulletins, form letters, etc., 1934 (Box 19, Folder 624)
  Schedule of Mailings: Foster Hall Publications, Vol. 1; Advertising booklet; Mailing lists; Lena B. Nofcier; Harold F. Brigham; Form letter dated September 18, 1934
- Record of Foster Hall entertainments, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 625)
  Foster Hall entertainments, 1935; Foster Hall Engagements; Foster Hall Calendar, Autumn, 1935; Foster Hall Engagement Book, September-June, 1933-1934; Foster Hall Engagement Book, September to June, 1933-1934; Foster Hall Engagement Book, September to June, 1932-1933; Foster Hall Calendar, Spring, 1935; Schedule of Foster Hall Entertainments for the Autumn Season, 1934
- Alabama, California, Colorado, Connecticut, Delaware, Washington, D.C., Florida and Georgia, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 626)
  Requests for arrangements of Foster melodies, Guzman Band arrangements and orchestra arrangements
- Idaho and Illinois, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 627)
- Indiana and Iowa, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 628)
- Kansas, Kentucky, Louisiana, Maine, Maryland, and Massachusetts, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 629)
- Michigan and Minnesota, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 630)
- Mississippi, Missouri, Montana and Nebraska, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 631)
- New Jersey, New Mexico, and New York, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 632)
- North Carolina and North Dakota, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 633)
- Ohio, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 634)
- Oklahoma and Oregon, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 635)
- Pennsylvania and Rhode Island, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 636)
- South Carolina, South Dakota, Tennessee and Texas, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 637)
- Utah, Vermont, Virginia, Washington, and West Virginia, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 638)
- Wisconsin and Wyoming, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 639)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Foreign Countries; Mr. Guzman, Mr. Manger, etc., 1936 (Box 20, Folder 640)
  Correspondence with Mr. Guzman and Mr. Manger; Requests for arrangements of Foster melodies, Guzman Band arrangements and orchestra arrangements
- U.S. Army and Navy, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 641)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Albania (Box 20, Folder 642)
  [Empty]
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Austria, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 643)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Belgium, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 644)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Bulgaria, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 645)
- Foreign Distribution of Stephen Foster Melodies, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 646)
  Spiral notebook with number of copies of the Guzman arrangement shipped out of the U.S.
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Canada, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 647)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Czechoslovakia, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 648)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Denmark, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 649)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Egypt, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 650)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Great Britain, 1937-1938 (Box 20, Folder 651)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Greece, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 652)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Hungary, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 653)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Italy, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 654)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Japan, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 655)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Yugoslavia, 1936-1937 (Box 20, Folder 656)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Latvia, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 657)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Mexico, 658 (Box 20, Folder 658)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Netherlands, 1937-1938 (Box 20, Folder 659)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Norway, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 660)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Poland, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 661)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Portugal, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 662)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Romania, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 663)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Siam, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 664)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Sweden, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 665)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Switzerland, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 666)
- Distribution of Guzman Band in Turkey, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 667)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Union of South Africa, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 668)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 669)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Yugoslavia, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 670)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in China, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 671)
  [empty]
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Estonia, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 672)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Finland, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 673)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in France, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 674)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Germany, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 675)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Irish Free State, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 676)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Lithuania, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 677)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley in Spain, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 678)
- Distribution of Guzman Band Medley Portugal, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 679)
- A, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 680)
  Correspondence with B.F. Aber; Mrs. Crosby Adams; Martha Rivers Adams; Nathaniel Anderson; Mrs. O.W. Adams; W.W. Anderson; William C. Agnew; Sister Aidan; P.J. Ailes; J.H. Kalbeutorn; Allentown Free Library; C.W. Allyn; Gladys Alter; M. Ambrose; American Antiquarian Society; American Autograph Shop; American Library Service; American Literature, Duke University; American Organist; American Phonograph Record Exchange; Martha M. Ames; Evelyn F. Morneweck; Bernice Amstead; D. Appleton-Century Company, Inc.; Apollo Music Co.; Mrs. George Archer; Enzo Archetti; Henry R. Armstrong; J.W. Arnold; Grace S. Arnold; Georgiana Lunt; A. Moran
- Form Letters, 1937-1938 (Box 20, Folder 681)
  Form Letter No. 1; Form Letter No. I-L; Form Letter No. 2; Form Letter No. 3; Form Letter No. 2-L; Form Letter No. 3-L; Form Letter No. 4; Form Letter No. 4-L; Form Letter No. 5; Form Letter No. 6; Form Letter No. 6-L
- B-BN, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 682)
  Correspondence with Mildred Bailey; Margaret W. Baker; B.R. Barber; Edwin N.C. Barnes; John Barnett; C.H. Bartlett; Helen Bastress; Bayerifche Staatsbibliothek; J.K. Lilly; Martha Beal; Estelle Bee; Essie Bell; Katherine Bell; Minerva M. Bennett; Paul E. Bergan; Muriel Bernitt; Stanley O. Bezanson; Bertha W. Bigelow; Mabel L. Bingler; C.C. Birchard and Company; C.C. Birchardito; Edward B. Birge; John E. Bishop; Dorothy Blackmar; William M. Blackwell; Alice Blews
- BO-BY, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 683)
  Correspondence with H.S. Gantor; Lloyd McGahey; Boston Athenaeum; Public Library of the City of Boston; Bowdoin College Library; Robert C. Bowers; W.C. Bowyer; Ronald Garmey; Alene Boyenton; Noss D. Brant; Florence Brantlinger; E. Balery; W. Masher; Allen Brown; Doris Brown; Janet Brown; Mary Brown; Priscilla Brown; G.T. Browne; Lois A. Reed; buffalo Public Library; Bulletin Index; Robert E. burke; H.M. Buswell; Mrs. Henry Butterfield; Ernest Buttrick; S.E. Byerly
- CA-CL, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 684)
  Correspondence with Jack L. Caiden; Cairo Public Library; J.J. Callahan; Lorena Callahan; G. Cappe; Frank R. Caputo; C. A. Carlisle; Margaret Carlisle; Arthur B. Carlson; Elvah Ferry; Mary Harris; George Revilo Carter; G.V. Chapin; Joseph Muller; D.J. Charlton; R. Elliot; Chicago Historical Society; Mrs. J. Smith Christy; Samuel Harden Church; E.L. Hutchins; Janet M. Clark; George H. Clapp; Vivian A. Blank; L.A. Eastman
- CO-CU, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 685)
  Wilma L. Cobb; Francis J. Cobban; Alfred Cobley; C.F. Coffin; inston Coleman; John Colla; Columbia University; Lawrence M. Conant; William Colker; Luella Clayton; James Brewster; James Francis Cooke; Leon Cooke; Katherine Copley; G.A. Cornell; Grace A. Courtney; Ethel Cox; Mrs. Warren Weston Creamer; I.B. Critchfield; Phillip Lee Crittanden; Richard Crooks; Henrietta Crosman; Cuyahoga County Library
- DA-DI, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 686)